[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Angelo Pizzo wrote Hoosiers, and David Anspaugh directed it. What other movie that is based on a true story did Pizzo co-produce and Anspaugh direct?", "correct_answer": "Rudy", "incorrect_answers": ["Rookie", "Glory Road", "Remember the Titans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Originally entitled Desert Song and released in 1972 by the band America, this song was banned in Kansas City for its supposed drug references.", "correct_answer": "A Horse with No Name", "incorrect_answers": ["Im Waiting for the Man", "Puff the Magic Dragon", "Heart of Gold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What would some species of  porcupine consume in order to supply calcium ans salts?", "correct_answer": "Bones", "incorrect_answers": ["Nails", "All of these", "Tiny rocks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brad Pitt was offered the lead role in this Tim Burton movie that was criticized for its violence and bloodshed.", "correct_answer": "Sleepy Hollow", "incorrect_answers": ["In Dreams", "Ed Wood", "Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Irish playwright, novelist and poet wrote the following line in his famous play Waiting for Godot: We are all born mad. Some remain so.", "correct_answer": "Samuel Beckett", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Hardy", "Marcel Proust", "Bernard Shaw"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the colonial settlement New Amsterdam located?", "correct_answer": "The state of New York", "incorrect_answers": ["UK", "New Jersey", "Holland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following are well known English puppets?", "correct_answer": "Punch and Judy", "incorrect_answers": ["Kukla Fran and Ollie", "Chip and Dale", "Thomas and Gerald"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The narwhale has two teeth in its upper jaw, one of which develops into a horn-like protrusion (this is true).\nIt is almost always the left one that  becomes the horn.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rank does James T. Kirk hold in the second Star Trek feature film, Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan (1982)?", "correct_answer": "Admiral", "incorrect_answers": ["Vice Admiral", "Captain", "Commodore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the codename of the operation in On Her Majestys Secret Service, aimed at the physical elimination of Ernst Stavro Blofeld?", "correct_answer": "Operation Bedlam", "incorrect_answers": ["Operation Firefly", "Operation  Mohican", "Operation Unicorn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these women was nicknamed The Iron Lady?", "correct_answer": "Margaret Thatcher", "incorrect_answers": ["Indira Gandhi", "Imelda Marcos", "Mother Teresa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term Fourth Estate refer to?", "correct_answer": "Press", "incorrect_answers": ["Judiciary", "Backward country", "Parliament"]}]